Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[woman screaming]
[man groaning, pig noises]
[woman yelling, indistinct]
[man] What the fuck?
[woman laughing]
[woman] I got you!
[pig squealing]
[man] Fuck...
[man and woman yelling]
[yelling continues]
[intense music]
[woman] Harper.
[soft moaning]
There's a police officer
here to see you.
Just wants to
ask you some questions.
I'll be back in an hour
to change your bandages
and it'll be time for you to go.
Harper Sykes. My name is Slayton.
I'm a state detective.
I gotta be honest. My boss
doesn't believe your story.
Thinks your little trip
through the Wachitumi Valley
is a hillbilly fairy tale.
Sent me down here to
find out if you're just another
mountain tweaker who
burned herself up in a meth lab.
And once you're
discharged she's gonna
lock you up for stabbing
the state trooper who found you.
[moans]
But I read his report.
And that's the reason I'm here.
See I've been hearing about
Wachitumi Valley
since I was a boy.
Those myths are legendary
where I come from.
I used to love to hear about
cop-killing Catholics
who didn't bury their dead,
runaway slaves still
practicing voodoo,
leftover Chinamen from
the railroad who ate their own.
But they were
just stories Harper.
That's all they were, no proof.
Never any answers.
No evidence.
So I came here
to get some answers
from your story
and you're going to have to
convince me that you got them.
Or we're going to lock you up.
Report says you were
covered in a slimy gauze.
Totally whacked out, you stabbed
a trooper in the arm with a knife.
You were about to
stab him again...
[Harper, muffled]
He was one of them one of them.
One of who?
[pained] He said plenty
more where they came from.
Who said that, Harper?
Who said that?
Ravener.
Who is he?
He killed Billy.
Billy.
Billy, right, Billy Harrison,
your missing boyfriend.
They've been ringing
the phone number you gave
for Billy and no answer.
Harper!
- No Billy.
- [screaming]
No Billy.
No boyfriend.
[screaming]
Billy's not missing.
Ravener killed him.
Where's his body?
I got guys out there
looking for bodies.
They haven't found a body.
Are you...
Are you batshit crazy, Harper?
Is that what you are?
You're just fucking out of your mind nuts?
Fuck you.
So you're a photographer, huh?
Take pictures
of animals in the wild.
I read your bio.
Pretty impressive.
Credited with
photographing two species
thought to be extinct that...
I guess that means
you're pretty good at your job.
[Harper moans]
What were you doing
in the Wachitumi Valley, Harper?
[Harper]
Looking for a red snake.
What's so special
amount of red snake?
[Harper]
We're not supposed to be there.
[shutter clicks]
[owl hoots]
[commotion in distance]
[dog barking]
[man laughing]
[whistling and whipping]
[barking and whipping continues]
[men shouting]
[men shouting continues,
indistinct]
[whistling]
[shutter clicks]
[car engine in distance]
[brakes screech]
[phone ringing, office chatter]
Hello.
[man] Hey, can I help you?
- ...with something?
- Hey, uh...
Yeah, I need to make a report.
Okay.
I saw something.
All right.
And?
You okay?
I took pictures on my camera.
All right.
Tell you what,
I'll make us some coffee.
And don't you go get what
it is that you want to show me
and then we can sort
it out, is that a deal?
Deal, yeah.
Oh, don't mind him.
I just hire him every once in a while
to keep him out of his mama's hair.
All right.
Have a seat.
[phone message] Hey, Harper, it's Billy,
just calling to give you an update.
I just left the city, I got about five
hours until I am in the Wachitumi Valley.
And, um, don't call me back,
I'm sure you're out there in the woods
taking photos,
being super cute, um...
I'm going to head right to the bed and
breakfast, I've got extra clothes for you.
[continues indistinct]
Hey, hey!
What the fuck!
Hey, stop!
No!
Somebody help!
[screaming]
You know, I was
on my way to Horsefeathers.
I was just gonna TGIF it.
You know? But I got a call
from the town retard
who said the sheriff had
had a little shutterbug visit.
You're a little snoop, huh?
He said you've been
putting your camera
where you aren't supposed to.
I'm a nature photographer
What?
- You can have my camera.
- I can't hear you.
You can have the camera.
Hmm.
I don't want the camera.
You can have the pictures.
[laughs]
I don't want the pictures.
I want you.
Okay?
Here's how it's going to go.
It's going to be super simple.
You and I we're just going
to duke it out right here. Pow.
These boys?
They're just here to make sure
I do my job. Okay?
So...
Come on out when you're
ready, sweetheart.
No rush.
Come on, it's showtime, lady.
Fuck.
Ow!
[Harper screams]
Yeah!
You are on the scoreboard.
These boys ain't got shit.
Look at you, huh?
I said I'd give you a fair
fight, getting a jump on me.
[pigs snort]
Where'd you learn
to shoot like that.
Oh, yeah! Ooh,
I'm falling for you.
- You're a psycho.
- Oh, I'm a psycho?
Girl, you just killed
yourself somebody.
Come here, you are exactly the type
of girl I have been looking for.
You really are.
You got spirit!
I swear to God, I mean, I...
[Harper coughs]
I'm falling for you.
I saw you.
At the tree tearing
that man apart.
That man...
That man was going
to tear my valley part.
That man was a timber
and mineral scout.
We caught him with samples.
You know what that
little fucker was gonna do?
He goes to a big oil company,
he gets a big fat check,
then they go and they lobby
and you know what happens
when the feds get to it?
They sell off the timber and mineral
rights to the highest bidder.
You ever been
to West Virginia?
You see what they've done
to their fucking mountains?
What I did was
preserve a way of life.
That fucker would have
changed everything. Everything!
I saw what you did.
Oh, fuck!
You don't understand, you stupid bitch.
I'm doing what I believe in. Hmm?
Just cause you believe in it
doesn't make it right.
Yes, it does!
You're not listening!
This place is mine!
[man laughing]
[Ravener] And I really thought
that you could appreciate this.
We've got the last old-growth
forest on the Atlantic seaboard.
It's just like when
the settlers got here.
Nature girl like you should be
able to appreciate all that.
[cows moo]
[birds coo]
[pants]
Hello?
[gasps]
[groaning]
Fuck!
[gurgled voices]
[flies buzzing]
[coughing]
[groaning]
[man screaming]
[owl hooting]
[man] Don't know why some
photo bitch is up here...
Probably sending her pictures
to some fucking prospector.
Man. [yells]
Ha ha ha.
You gonna come here...
Force me out of the valley. I ain't
gonna have that, yeah, I'm gonna find it.
I'm gonna catch her...
[gunshots]
I'm gonna break her. [gunshots]
I'm gonna break that bitch!
Little cunt.
Dumb fucking bitch.
Oh...
[yells]
[yells indistinctly]
Come on, bitch!
Where you at?
[man laughs]
[laughs louder]
Little Red Riding Hood,
come back out of the forest, huh?
[howling]
Where's that devil?
[groans]
Fucking... [indistinct]
[indistinct shout]
Woo-wee!
Yeah. Yeah.
Huh? [indistinct]
You hear me?
[man mumbling indistinct]
What do you think...?
[gunshots, Harper screaming]
[man moaning]
[screams]
Help.
[mumbling]
[coughing]
How do we get out of here?
[groaning]
You ain't ever gonna
get out of here.
[laughs]
I took you on that [indistinct].
Just so you know. [laughs]
I had...
I had you good.
[laughs]
You ain't nothing.
[muffled screaming]
[screams]
[dirt bike in distance]
[dirt bike revs]
[bike crashes]
[panting]
[thunder rumbles]
[man over radio]
Jesse, you there?
Jesse?
Harper Sykes.
Guess you'd be off squawking
away. Had to be you.
You left your wallet in the
truck, so I looked you up a bit.
Googled ya.
A month in Arkansas looking for
the ivory-billed woodpecker,
then hunting
tigers in Asia.
You're G.I. Jane with a camera.
You're the real deal.
Now, you're wondering
if I'm going to hear you coming
and try to ride that
rig out of there.
You're wondering whether
it's worth the risk.
Well, here's the thing. There's
only one way out of the valley.
Burning Falls to the north
is impassable.
The gas station
is a 16-day hike to the west.
And it's going
to take you nearly a month
if you try to go through
the national forest east.
The only way out of there
is coming down the river
and you know that's gonna
happen sooner or later...
[loud music]
Hello?
[faint music playing]
Oh.
Good to see you.
Mallinckrodt.
Harper Sykes.
Sykes.
Very good. Wonderful name.
Want a bourbon?
Yes, yes, you do.
Could I use your phone?
I don't have a phone, ma'am.
I haven't had a phone
for 15 years.
Oh.
[background rambling continues]
I just really need
to make a phone call.
Um, let's go in there
by the fire and get you sorted.
[groans]
Every time I spill
just a little bit.
You know what I mean?
Daytime drinking.
[sighs]
You're wondering.
This is for my heart,
all of this stuff.
One, two, three, this, four.
This, uh, comes with my
supplies once a week.
- Your supplies.
- Mm-hm.
Everything here is delivered
to me once a week.
And allows me to stay here.
Those books there.
They're a document of how
we tamed this valley.
Felled trees
from all around here
Went down to the river
and got big stones
and brought them up here.
And that's when there were
mosquitoes bigger than hummingbirds.
And there were bears running
around killing people.
It was grim, but we did it.
We built this place.
We tamed this whole valley.
- It's a lot of death.
- That there?
[chuckles] That's the progress
of civilization.
Progress?
Of course.
What do you mean progress?
Societies have long
distinguished themselves
in how they killed their own.
Seems like torture.
No, no, torture's
a whole different matter.
Execution is the measurement
of a country's civility.
Torture is the barometer
of a nation's creativity.
How do you kill people?
How do you keep a man alive
enough to get him to say
what you need him to say?
And everybody had
different ways of doing it.
Proudly named their methods.
The Spanish Donkey
the Iron Maiden.
And there was a cruel,
cruel competition
between the Kings of Pain.
But what do you think scares
man more than anything else?
What do you think
scares him the most?
Mother Nature.
Because Mother Nature
is the true Lord of Pain.
- Want another drink?
- No, thanks.
I'm going to have one,
if you don't mind.
[man warbling in background]
I know you didn't ask for it.
There you go.
You murder it.
Wow.
Thatta girl.
[alarm clock sounds]
While I do this can you come over
here and turn this thing off?
[groans]
Ah.
[alarm stops]
[sighs]
Oh, my God.
You motherfucking bitch.
[coughs]
Sykes.
Sykes!
Goddamnit!
[coughs]
Sykes!
[muffled] I know what you
saw down at the river.
Where you were taking
your pictures.
What you saw was a hollow cross.
I, uh, came up
with that myself.
You run on along.
They're waiting for you.
[door closes]
[panting]
[engine idles]
[engine starts]
[radio] ...continue to
indicate a severe thunderstorm
capable of producing large damaging
hail up to golf-ball size...
The severe storm...
...capable of producing large,
damaging hail up to golf-ball size.
The severe storm
is located near Presbiet...
or about over Presbiet and moving
southeast at 30 miles per hour.
Further locations
in the warning include
East Mandura
Western Pierce...
This is a dangerous situation.
If you are in the path of this storm,
prepare immediately for destructive hail
which can significantly damage
roofs, windows, siding and vehicles.
Seek shelter now inside a sturdy
structure and stay away from windows.
Report any damage to the
nearest law enforcement agency
for relay to the National
Weather Service.
- [gunshot]
- [radio emergency sound]
[radio emergency signal]
[indistinct radio]
[engine sputters]
[engine slows to a stop]
[thunder rumbles]
[screams]
[bell on door jungles]
Hello?
Hey? Hello?
Darlene, damn pump's
out again. Darlene?
I'm going to take my revolver out
and put it down on the ground.
Billy and I have been looking
for you since yesterday.
Where you been?
That boyfriend of yours
has covered nearly every inch
of this valley looking for you.
[sobs]
It's okay.
Okay.
[continues sobbing]
Where'd you run off to? Huh?
I found your truck.
I got all your stuff in my cruiser.
Alright?
It'll be okay.
Let's go.
Can you tell me what happened?
I'm running from them.
Who?
I'll show you.
[loud music]
No! No! No!
[screaming]
[cow moos]
In ancient times the Slavs
used to get answers from people
by using their cows
for more than just milk.
You see, digesting all the food
that one of these guys
eats in a day,
that requires
a very special system.
So these big beautiful beasts
they have four stomachs.
They're basically
just a big old vat
of the world's most toxic acid.
A long time ago
there were these
- two dairy farmers [indistinct].
- [cow moos]
And they had overthrown
this horrid king
who was famous
for his most wicked ways.
He just loved torture.
He loved impalements.
He loved Judas cradles.
He loved coffin tortures.
All the good stuff.
Now, these brothers, they'd
sacked the castle, right?
And the king, who obviously has
no idea about his predicament,
he just offers up his kingdom.
Throws the queen and his
children and the village
if they'll just let
his cowardly ass go. [chuckles]
These revolutionaries...
- they're just simple
- [cow moos]
little dairy farmers.
And to them, you know,
this doesn't sound right.
- [gunshot]
- [Harper screams]
[cow thuds]
So... they throw a huge banquet
in the king's court.
Everybody's there,
the whole royal family.
The brothers are sitting there and
they're all just having a grand time.
Then somebody leads a cow in.
One of the brothers, he gets up.
He goes to the banquet table
and he takes
out a huge carving knife.
[cow grunts]
Then the dairy farmer
takes a knife.
He creates a small cavity
just below the anus.
Then the other brother,
he binds the king's feet.
And his hands.
And then to everyone's shock,
they slide the king
inside the cow.
They start stitching up
around the king's neck.
These Slavs had seen it all.
[chuckles]
Their king...
with a head sticking
out of a calf.
This was new
this was groundbreaking.
[flies buzzing]
They said it took about three days
for the king's body to decompose.
[laughs]
What are you laughing at?
[laughing]
I saw the picture of all of you
at the old man's house.
That's what you're laughing at?
I killed all of them.
Yeah. I blew that
Kinsey guy's face off.
And the tweaker...
He got shot to pieces.
And then that creepy guy
with the smile.
Lost his head.
And that old sick demented fuck.
He had himself a meth-induced
heart attack.
He was in a lot of pain.
So I shot him.
Yeah, I got your
whole fucked-up clan.
[laughs]
Well, there's a lot more
where that came from.
You're the coward
who couldn't find me.
You get some tired cop
to come pick me up?
Untie me.
So I can claw
your fucking face off.
- Oh?
- Yeah.
I'm going to torture you.
- You are?
- Yeah.
And then I'm gonna kill you.
Yeah.
Then...
I'm going to drag you across...
the floor over to that door.
I'm going to watch the pigs
- tear you apart.
- [rope cutting]
[knife drops to ground]
- Come on.
- You motherfucker!
[screaming]
I got you, you motherfucker!
[laughs maniacally]
I got you, you motherfucker.
[breathes heavily]
No?
Harper!
[gunshot]
[screaming]
[nurse] The doctor is waiting
for you with the lab results.
And it's time for you to go.
[Harper] Wait.
I'm almost done.
After he beat me...
And no one cares...
[indistinct]
After he stabbed me.
After he fed my boyfriend
to his pig.
No!
[pig squeals]
After he hung me upside down
and left me for dead.
After he terrorized me.
After he butchered a cow.
And gutted it.
After stitching...
Where are you going, Ginger?
You're gonna miss the best part.
I think you're ill.
I think you are the victim of a
dangerous opioid epidemic and...
you're troubled, and you and
whoever you're hanging out with...
pose a great danger
to yourselves.
[man] Detective Slayton,
shut the door, please.
In your officer's report
it says my patient was covered
in a Vaseline-like substance
and that her burns
- are the likely result of an explosion.
- I know all that.
She wasn't covered in Vaseline.
And it wasn't heat which
created her third degree burns.
What kind of burns are they?
The lab report states
that she was embalmed
in the digestive enzymes
of ox bile.
She was being digested.
[inhales]
[car starts]
[music starts]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ Blind faith stepping
out in the wind ♪
♪ Won't ya learn
surrender again ♪
♪ Are you happy living this
moment cause this ♪
♪ This moment
is your life ♪
♪ Burnt my bright stars
searching through the heavens ♪
♪ No beginning and no end ♪
♪ Like a driftwood
flowing down the river ♪
♪ Throughout all eternity ♪
♪ Well there's nothing left
really for me to prove ♪
♪ But to feel your
connection in life ♪
♪ Spend my time walking
thin gilded road for some ♪
♪ False identity and lie ♪
♪ Climbing branches
looking at the heavens ♪
♪ Knowing truth
is what I need ♪
♪ I fell in the deep dark
journeyed to the roots end ♪
♪ Turning ashes into seeds ♪
♪ Till you get enough ♪
♪ Felt the thunderbirds crash
down on the dry lands ♪
♪ Out and down
on desolation road ♪
♪ Such a bittersweet tear
knowing why we exist here ♪
♪ One fleeting moment
and we'll go ♪
♪ I always see her
as the mother ♪
♪ While these other
parts want her ♪
♪ Numbering you,
craving you all the time ♪
♪ Meanwhile, learning patience
four years alone ♪
♪ Spent learning,
healing, walking ♪
♪ Fucking the line ♪
♪ Before I go ♪
♪ Chin up ♪
♪ And heal ♪
♪ Let me see your face ♪
♪ I can feel ♪
♪ All your shield ♪
♪ Let me love you
while I'm here ♪
♪ Let me love you... ♪